

Mohamad Sina Kheiri

Front-End Developer(Next.js/React.js)

As a Front-end developer with 4 years of experience, I possess a diverse skill set of 25+ technical abilities. With a strong focus on delivering clean code, high-quality projects and exceptional user interfaces, I am committed to staying up-to-date with the latest industry trends and best practices.

I also have the knowledge and skills for UI Design and I have created User personas, Wireframes, High fidelity projects and Prototypes using Figma and Adobe XD.

- sinakheiri.dev@gmail.com
- +989100056440
- Karaj, Alborz, Iran

- https://sinakheiri.dev
- https://github.com/IWarwolfl
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohamad-sina-kheiri

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end(Next.js) Developer

Remote in Exmodules (website - twitter) 2023 - 2024

- Led a team of developers and provided guidance on project requirements.
- Created seamless user interfaces for various projects(+10).
- Learned and improved skills in Next.js, TypeScript, and Tailwind CSS.
- Delved into **Web3** world and worked with Metamask and Smart Contracts to develope crypto based websites.

Front-end(React.js) Developer

Full-time in Agahpadidar (linkedin) 2021 - 2023

- Established connections to Restful APIs using **Async Thunks** and **Axios**.
- Utilized **Redux toolit** for state management
- Participated in **Agile development** methodologies such as daily stand-ups and sprint planning.

SKILLS

- Programming languages

Javascript, Typescript, HTML5, CSS3, SCSS

- Frameworks

Next.js, Material UI, Tailwind CSS

State Management

Zustand, Redux toolkit

- Testing

Jest

- Libraries

Web3, GSAP, Lenis, TanStack Query, React hook form, zod, React.js, Swiper, Axios, Formik, Yup, Recharts.js, Jquery

- UI Design

Figma, Adobe XD, Responsive Web Design, Adobe Illustrator

- Other

shadon/ui, Git, Github, Agile Methodoligies, Clean **Code Principles**

Frontend Developer and UI Designer

Freelance in ponisha(<u>link</u>)

2018 - 2021

- Designed **User interfaces** for mobile apps and websites.
- Created User personas, Wireframes, High fidelity designs, and integrated Prototyping.
- Developed static web pages and HTML templates.

EDUCATION

Islamic Azad University Of Karaj

Bachelor Degree, Computer Software Engineering

2022 - present

Shahid Beheshti University

Associate degree, Biomedical Engineering 2019 – 2022

LANGUAGES

Persian(mother tongue)
English(Advanced)

PROJECTS [viewable by attached links and code is available in my github]

-BlockT[Front-end Development(Next.js - Web3)]

BlockT is my personal **Web3** project and My goal was to work with web3 to connect to **Smart contracts** and send transactions on Ethereum Sepolia testnet in this project.

-<u>Farzam.at</u>[Front-end Development(Next.js)]

Farzam.at is a startup project for design and coding services that I have collaborated on.

- Portfonext[Front-end Development(Next.js)]

Portfonext is my personal **portfolio** project that is currently under development.

It showcases my abilities in **front-end development**, **UI design** and **up-to-date technologies**.

- <u>Bluetek</u> [Front-end Development(Vanilla)]

- Blue Wallet [UI/UX Design]

As a key contributor to the Bluetek project, I designed and developed 5 unique landings and profiles and I app that were both **visually appealing and user-friendly** and met the requirements of a **crypto-based** website and app.

- <u>Modernist</u> [Front-end Development(Vanilla)]

Modernist is a personal project that showcases my expertise in designing a **Customizable HTML Template**.

- Park Speedy [UI/UX Design]

Park Speedy is a Figma project that showcases my **UI/UX design** skills for a startup app aimed at solving parking space issues.